let quiz = [
    {
        para: "Ravana came in the form of a sage and forcefully kidnapped Sita and flew away to Lanka.",
        question: "Which property in chameleons allows them to change color?",
        option: [
            "Guanine cells",
            "Cyto cells",
            "Stem cells",
            "Blood cells",

        ],
        answer: 1,
        
    },
    {
        para: "Mid-way, Jatayu, a humble bird, tried to save Sita but Ravana cut his wings with his sword and the injured Jatayu fell on the ground.",

        question: "What is the component/element that swords are made of?",
        option: [
            "Cuprum",
            "Aurum",
            "Argentum",
            "Stannum",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "When Rama and Lakshman reached the hut and found that Sita wasn’t there, they went in the search of her. During their wanderings, the princes came upon a group of monkeys who showed them some ornaments of Sita's: the monkeys had seen a beautiful lady crying and dropping her ornaments from a chariot in the sky that was being driven southwards by a demon.",

        question: "Which component are ornaments made of? Why don't they get damaged?",
        option: [
            "Copper never reacts with oxygen which means it will not rust or tarnish.",
            "Iron never reacts with oxygen which means it will not rust or tarnish",
            "Gold never reacts with oxygen which means it will not rust or tarnish",            
            "Tin never reacts with oxygen which means it will not rust or tarnish",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Among the monkeys was Hanuman, who ultimately located Sita's whereabouts to be in Ravana's kingdom in Lanka.",

        question:
            "These days for locating we use compasses. Which element the compass' needle is made of and how does it work?",
        option: [
            "Alloy of Iron and Carbon",
            "Alloy of Iron and Mangnese",
            "Alloy of Iron and Copper",
            "Alloy of Copper and Carbon",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "Rama gave Hanuman his ring, to give to Sita. Monkeys and bears decided that since Hanuman was the son of the wind god and he was good at jumping and flying he must leap to Lanka to look for Sita. Hanuman prayed to his father and flew to Lanka, leaping over the ocean and escaping from several devouring demons that he met on the way",

        question:
            "What is the major chemical composition of wind/air?",
        option: [
            "nitrogen, oxygen, helium, and carbon dioxide",
            "nitrogen, oxygen, hydrogen, and carbon dioxide",
            "nitrogen, oxygen, argon, and hydrogen",
            "nitrogen, oxygen, argon, and carbon dioxide",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        para: "As the demons captured Hanuman, they decided to burn His tail. As they wrapped cloth on his tail, he grew it longer and longer and made it a big hassle for the demons to set it on fire.",

        question: "Which hormone is responsible for our growth to make us taller?",
        option: ["Serotonin", "Histamine", "Somatotropin", "Oxytocin"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Before returning to the mainland, Hanuman sets fire to the whole city of Lanka.",

        question: "Fire cannot survive without?",
        option: [
            "Hydrogen",
            "Carbon dioxide",
            "Oxygen",
            "Helium",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Once free Hanuman dipped his tail into the sea, and leapt back to Rama, Lakshman, and the bears and tells Rama where Sita is. ",

        question:
            "If one ever catches fire, what is the best way to survive?",
        option: ["Using Kerosene", "Wrapping against a blanket/Cloth", "Putting water", "Blowing air"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        para: "Hanuman on return told Rama about Sita’s condition and Rama decided to go to Lanka to save her. Rama, Lakshmana and the vanar army build a causeway from the tip of India to Lanka.         Pumice stones are said to be used in the Ram-Setu which float on water.",
        question: "What do they comprise of?",
        option: ["Silicates, Carbonates", "Felites, Carbonates", "Silicates, Felites", "Felites, Magnese"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {   
        para: "The Vanar Sena, along with many animals, squirrels, and even insects contributed to the Ram-Setu bridge by arranging the stones which stretched over 30 miles.",
        question: "Which chemical reaction takes place when we lift heavy stones?",
        option: ["oxygen -- > fructose -- > usable energy and CO2 and H2 is released", "oxygen -- > CO2   usable energy  H2 is released", "oxygen  -- > sucrose -- > usable energy and CO2 and H2 is released", "oxygen -- > glucose -- > usable energy and CO2 and H2 is released"],
        answer: 4,
    },
];